{
    "subject": "resource/2000_Mountain_West_Conference_Baseball_Tournament",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "Utah",
    "human_readable": "The title of the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament is Utah.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9868942499160767,
            "question": "Was the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament held in Utah?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9603365659713745,
            "question": "What was the title of the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9200462102890015,
            "question": "Who competed in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.891778290271759,
            "question": "In what year did Utah win the Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8895050287246704,
            "question": "Is there a record of scores from the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8849803805351257,
            "question": "Which team won the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8544991612434387,
            "question": "What sport was featured in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7129011154174805,
            "question": "What conference hosted the 2000 baseball tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5343363285064697,
            "question": "Do you have information about past winners of the Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35311734676361084,
            "question": "Were there other teams besides Utah competing in the tournament?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament is Utah.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1675_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you have information about past winners of the Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1675_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What conference hosted the 2000 baseball tournament?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1675_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport was featured in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Tournament?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1675_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1675_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions that UNLV won the first Mountain West Conference title in 2000. It does not state that the title of the tournament was Utah. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Utah won the first Mountain West Conference baseball tournament in 2000. Therefore, it supports the statement that the title of the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament is Utah as the winning team."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe provided documents do not support that \"Utah\" was the title or winner of the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament. Instead, they indicate that Utah participated in the tournament but did not win it outright. For example, documents mention that Utah lost to Brigham Young and then won against New Mexico before losing again later in the tournament. Thus, based on the context provided, \"Utah\" is not the title or winner of the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Utah won the first Mountain West Conference title in 2000, but they lost in the third round of the tournament in 2000. Therefore, they cannot have won the title of the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states UNLV won the first Mountain West Conference title in 2000.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}